<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on UIMIM</title><link>https://uim.im/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on UIMIM</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uim.im/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advanced Post Demo</title><link>https://uim.im/posts/second-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uim.im/posts/second-post/</guid><description>A basic blog post example with intro and optional on-page title override
Heading With Class Note that you&amp;rsquo;ll need to include the ! to override color because this is in a .prose block unless you edit the uno.config.ts to use inherit color override under the typography.
Notice that the class is text-$c-brand-light; $c-brand-light = var(--c-brand-light)
You can set class with inline html if goldmark is unsafe.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://uim.im/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uim.im/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Yeah, but your scientists were so preoccupied with whether or not they could, they didn&amp;rsquo;t stop to think if they should. Jaguar shark! So tell me - does it really exist? Remind me to thank John for a lovely weekend. Hey, you know how I&amp;rsquo;m, like, always trying to save the planet? Here&amp;rsquo;s my chance.
Must go faster&amp;hellip; go, go, go, go, go! You really think you can fly that thing?</description></item><item><title>Lorem Markdownum</title><link>https://uim.im/posts/lorem-markdownum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://uim.im/posts/lorem-markdownum/</guid><description>Amens nitentior vires Lorem markdownum Argo est praebebant Andros erat, tibi parte montibus erunt venis tacita spernimus more. Olim erat Aiax dixi factas potens. Perque natus ipsa potenti; nunc parte precor in mortalis manant bellica, umbrosaque et. Inrita videtur regnum, in est vulnere inductae Ilion et feruntur Latiae famulus nec dederat uteroque lenita fraternaque horrenda omnia.
Maris Circe victum suggerit et conscia dixit Habes et undis carinae fundae lilia coniecit Tot nomine ire tot fassusque nobis ad Geminas iugales mille et ingenium magna agitantem Nemo quae sedemque Iunone Theseius abstulit morabar mersis Isto supremo, genitor Phoronidos, honos ibi lacus saepe rogato properus: sum an vetantis.</description></item></channel></rss>